(Sheldon:)That's ridiculous.
(Sheldon:)I am one of the great minds
of our generation.
(Sheldon:)I work on a level so rarified,
you couldn't even imagine it.
(Sheldon:)I said, stop looking at my cool train!
Hm. A strange place to put a picture
of you and Bernadette.
Well, I've wanted everybody
to know I love my wife, you know...
(Howard:)...and nobody to know
I forgot to turn off the laser.
(Raj:)They're here.
Our action figures have arrived.
It's the best $500 I've ever spent.
(Leonard:)A thousand dollars on action figures?
How can you afford that?
Easy. His family is loaded
and Bernadette has a great job.
My wife came with both funbags
and moneybags.
Say hello to an exact-scale model of me.
(Raj:)Oh, I'm not dark chocolate.